<Summary>
* Tower Craft - The Marching Mushrooms
* Team Double Check
*	Chulseung Lee
*	Jeesoo Kim
*	Sangmin Kim
*	Minseok Sung
* Tower Craft is a grid based 2D tower defense game where the user have to protect the incoming enemies by installing various towers. 
*	User must upgrade the towers to defeat the enemies that grow stronger as the game proceeds.
* All content © 2019 DigiPen (USA) Corporation, all rights reserved

<Installation Instructions>
	Open the TowerCraft_Setup.exe 
	ShootingCraft.exe will be created in C:\Program Files (x86)\DigiPen\TowerCraft folder

<Source>
	Sadly, the framework engine we had used was expired and could not get the engine back.
	However, you can still take a look on the source code in the SOURCE folder.

<How To Play>
	User must stop the enemies by installing towers beside the enemy path.
	There are 5 lives and everytime an enemy reaches the castle, a life is dissolved.
	Enemies get stronger every wave, so stronger towers are needed.
	After defeating each enemy, user earns gold that can be used to purchase new towers or to upgrade them. 
	User must carefully decide which tower to install and upgrade since there are limited amount of gold.
	The goal is to protect the tower until the last enemy wave. 

<Controls>
	All controls are done with the mouse click. No keyboard inputs required to play the game. 
	F - fullscreen
	ESC - shut down game

<Cheat Codes>
	Right click to earn free gold.